traveleurope.com 2012-12-04

# Privacy policy - Traveleurope.com

By using **Traveleurope** website, you accept the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time to take account of changing requirements such as changes in technology or legislation, and request that you refer back to this Policy frequently to become aware of any such revisions. In addition, we recommend that you review the privacy policy of any website accessed through the **Traveleurope** website as these sites may be subject to different privacy practices. **Traveleurope** is not responsible for these websites or for the information made available thereon.

## Security and Confidentiality

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We use Secure Socket Layers (SSL) technology to ensure the privacy of the information provided to us both in the hotel booking engine and in any other order form. At no time are the customers debit/credit card details transmitted un-encrypted over the Internet. When you make bookings online or access your personal profile you can do so through a secure server. The use of Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology means that all personal information, such as your credit card number, will be encrypted as it travels from your computer to the **Traveleurope** Online Booking Engine. When received, the information is processed by a secured Payment Gateway. If your browser supports SSL, and if you entered our site via our secure server access, then transmission of any sensitive data will be protected. If your browser does not support SSL, we recommend that you upgrade to the latest version of any browser to enhance the security of further transactions, otherwise the transmission of your personal data may not be protected and **Traveleurope** disclaims any responsibility in this regard. We also operate behind a firewall to ensure there is no unauthorised access to our systems.

## Information required to process your booking

We do not collect personal information about you when you browse the **Traveleurope** website. However, if you wish to book a property using the site's interactive services, we will require you to complete the Booking Form and provide us with certain information which may include the following:

  1. Name
  2. Postal Address
  3. Credit/Debit Card number and expiration date
  4. Billing address
  5. Phone numbers
  6. E-mail address
  7. Travel details

## Cookies

We are constantly researching the latest in technology to ensure that we are able to give you the most effective, informative and enjoyable experience on our site. A cookie is a small text file that our site may send to your hard drive when you are logged on to our site. They uniquely identify a single computer and provide us with statistical and other analytical information collected on an aggregate and non-individual specific basis helping us to improve website browsing and users' experience. We do not use cookies to store personal information. At any stage you may decide to disable cookies. If you want to know when our site is using a cookie from your hard drive, you can set your browser to send you an alert. If you prefer to use our site without utilising cookies, you can set your browser to not accept them at all, however, they will make your life easier. Many web sites are employing this cookie technology and cookies are never to be used to store information of a private nature, such as credit card numbers. Also, you can be assured that the information stored in any cookies initiated by **Traveleurope** cannot be accessed by any other web sites. Please also refer to your browser Help instructions for further details.

## Who sees your information

We use your personal information to process your booking and to deliver relevant information to you in connection with your reservation (booking confirmation, cancellation, feedback). To process your order we will share some of your details with the hotel, or other involved third party. We will provide only the information necessary to ensure the successful fulfilment of your travel arrangements. Your personal information and any records relating to your travel will also be retained for audit functions. We do not sell customer names or other private profile information to third parties and have no intention of doing so in the future. With your explicit approval, we may use the personal information to provide you with information which we think you may find of interest. This may include information about services, products, special offers and promotions offered by Traveleurope or other service providers. We may contact you by any means of communication for which you have given us contact details, including by post, e-mail, pop-up window, fax and telephone.

## Right of rectification or erasure

You may ask to have your personal data corrected, if inaccurate, or erased if they are no longer needed to provide the purchased booking service, by sending an email to [customer@traveleurope.it](mailto:customer@traveleurope.it)
